Burn it all down.
Scream 7 is a horror, mystery, crime film directed by Kevin Williamson.
When a new Ghostface killer emerges in the quiet town where Sidney Prescott has built a new
life, her darkest fears are realized as her daughter becomes the next target.
Determined to protect her family, Sidney must face the horrors of her
past to put an end to the bloodshed once and for all.
Sidney Prescott, played by Neve Campbell.
Gale Weathers, played by Courteney Cox.
Tatum Evans, played by Isabel May.
Mindy Meeks-Martin, played by Jasmin Savoy Brown.
Chad Meeks-Martin, played by Mason Gooding.
Scream 7 is an upcoming American slasher film directed by Kevin Williamson from a screenplay
he co-wrote with Guy Busick, from a story by James Vanderbilt and Busick.
It is a sequel to Scream VI (2023) and the seventh
installment in the Scream film series.
The film stars Neve Campbell, Courteney Cox, Jasmin Savoy Brown, and Mason Gooding reprising their roles from previous films, alongside Isabel May, Anna Camp,
Joel McHale, Mckenna Grace, Michelle Randolph, Jimmy Tatro, Asa Germann, Celeste O'Connor, Sam Rechner, Ethan Embry, Tim Simons, and Mark Consuelos.
The film follows a new Ghostface killer who targets Sidney Prescott's daughter.
Following the exit of Scream (2022) and Scream VI directors Matt Bettinelli-Olpin and Tyler
Gillett in August 2023, Christopher Landon was hired to direct the seventh Scream film.
However, the film went through a creative retooling after the departure of stars Melissa
Barrera and Jenna Ortega in late 2023, with Landon also exiting the project.
In March 2024, Campbell confirmed her return to the franchise after being absent from Scream VI, with Williamson
hired to direct Scream 7 after serving as writer and producer of the early films in the series.
Filming began in January 2025 and concluded that March.
Scream 7 is scheduled to be released in the United States on
February 27, 2026, by Paramount Pictures.
The film explores themes of mask, sequel, murder, serial killer, slasher.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.